NO BOY NO CRY ore zenshin GO
no boy, no cry, I advance go!
shounen yo kiite kure
hey boys, listen up
ningen nante taishita mon ja nai sa
humans aren't such a big deal
ashita nante moui ranai kara
who needs tomorrow anyway
nigitta kobushi wo kakusu na yo
so don't hide your fists
fuan ni yume wo
you're not old enough
uri tobasu hodo mada oiborechainai daro
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
shounen yo kokoro no jyuu no
hey boys, you're the only ones
hikigane wo hikeru no wa kimi dake sa
who can pull the trigger in your heart
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
doushi yo mo naku kudaranai
we're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
kono subarashii sekai ni tattaima ikiteiru kara
awesome world right at this moment,
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
subete no hontou to uso wo
don't forget every truth or lie
kesshite wasurete shima wa nai you ni
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
shinu ni wa mosugiru darou
we're way too young to die
shiraketa tsura ga naranderu karappo no kono machi de
in this empty town lined with empty faces
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids took off
kaze no nai kono yoru ni
into this windless night
nanika wo kaeyou to shiteru kara
because they want to change something
Tearful
Yell!
You Are My Friend
That's Naruto?
What is this intimidating power?
And what was that
red Chakra earlier on?
Is this guy a monster?
What the hell are you?!
Your friend!
That's why I'm telling you
I'm not gonna let the likes
of Orochimaru get you!
I'm telling you that I'll stop you...
even if it means breaking
every bone in your arms and legs!
Fire Style:
Fire Ball Jutsu!
Come on! Wake up already!
If you don't come to your senses
I'll have to break your bones
so that you can't move
and I'll take you home that way, Sasuke!
Shut up...
What the hell do you
who has neither parents nor brothers,
think you understand?
What makes you think that you
who's been all alone from the start
can understand anything about me?!
It's because I have the ties
that I feel this agony.
How could you possibly understand...
what it feels like to lose all that!
It's true that I can't understand...
how it feels to really
have parents or brothers...
However...
It's my treat today...
Eat your fill!
Yippee!
When I'm with Iruka-sensei
I imagine...
— Dig in!
Shinobi, first of all need, to
warm their inner man.
Hey! Hey! Don't get too carried away
and overeat!
If this is...
what it feels like to have a dad.
When I'm with you...
Idiot, idiot, idiot...
What was that, useless?!
I'm not gonna lose to you
no matter what!
Go ahead and say
whatever you want.
How about this?
Better not start feeling
too comfortable.
I wonder... if having a brother
feels something like that.
Why is it Naruto...?
Why is it that you go to
this extent for me...?
For me it's a tie that
I've finally been able to have!
That's why I'm gonna stop you.
It's too late, Naruto...
It's already too late.
I can't go back anymore.
Come Naruto!
In that case,
I just have to cut that tie.
Cut, huh?
Then why wear that headband now?
I'll acknowledge you...
You're strong.
And the reason for that is
you're someone who knows
the pain of solitude as I do.
And that pain makes people stronger.
And for that very reason
by cutting that tie
I will be able to obtain
even greater strength.
I will fight you now on equal terms.
However...
You won't even be able to
inflict a scratch on my forehead.
That's something that
won't change in the least.
It seems that whatever I say
won't have any effect anymore, huh?
Sasuke!
I'm done with talking...
From here on it's only fighting.
Come!
I'm able to see...
I'm now able to see
this guy's movements...
which I wasn't able to see before.
I'm able to see them!
Sasuke's moving completely
different from a few moments ago.
But I couldn't care less!
In any case, I can't afford to lose!
Damn it!
It must be the influence of my body
getting used to the state of Curse Mark.
When he moves...
by the subtle movements in
the way he exerts his strength...
I can vividly see
an image of his next move.
With my level of "eyes",
I don't need to use unnecessary Chakra
and can instead preserve it.
The Curse Mark takes
too much Chakra.
If I can see this much...
I can time my attacks to the images of
Naruto's movements as I foresee them.
This is no good...
He's totally reading my movements.
Damn it!
Oh, there you are.
There's no mistake it's this way, right?
Right.
We better hurry.
I have a bad premonition.
Sasuke!
Fire Style:
Dragon Flame Jutsu!
Sa-su-ke...
It's too late, Naruto.
It's too late now! Naruto!
You're weak aren't you, kid?
You better be grateful to me...
and to the Fourth Hokage
who contained me within
the likes of you!
What's going on?
What was that just now?
Even if I'm able to read
Naruto's movements completely...
his Chakra makes
a separate move of its own.
It seems like the Chakra itself is moving
in accordance with its own will...
Even with my "eyes"
I'm unable to read it completely.
That red Chakra...
that's not an ordinary Chakra!
Your target is Naruto after all.
To abduct Naruto-kun
is the No.1 priority
placed by our organization, Akatsuki!
I see...
It appears that you have
some kind of special power.
Now I understand!
Fire Style:
Fire Ball Jutsu!
That Chakra is protecting him?!
Calm down.
I won't be caught as long as
I fight from a distance.
Damn it... This is incredible!
All I can do is dodge...
Please let me get there in time.
Damn it, gimme a break...
If I get tainted by this power...
I don't even know what
will happen to me in the end...
But it can't be helped
can it, Naruto?
It is certainly true
that you were special...
However...
I am even more special than you.
Sasuke!
hitotsu hitotsu omoidaseba
when I recalled the parts one by one,
subete wakatteita kigashite ita no ni
I felt as though I had understood everything
iroaseta kotoba wa
faded words
boku no sugu soba ni oite atta
which I kept so close to me
kotae no denai yoru to
speechless nights,
a hint of warmth,
hitokira no nukumori to
and this distant yearning for you
haruka kanata no akogare to
I live,
tada sore dake wo
simply repeating this cycle
kurikaeshi boku wa ikite iru
held in my two hands
kono ryoute ni kakaete iru mono
a droplet of time
toki no shizuku
softly clutching forgotten memories
sotto nigirishimete wasureta kioku
lost words
nakushita kotoba
I'll keep these thoughts...
kono omoi wa
Damn! My body hurts!
And to make it worse
I've completely lost feeling
in my left arm!
Apparently this power
isn't something that
I can just keep on using continuously!
But... I can't give up!
My next blow is
going to be the end!
Next time:
"Concluded in a Rain of Tears."